https://www.automaticcoating.com/privacy-statement

416-335-7500HomeCareersContactCompany Profile About PIPE LINE COATING Capabilities WHAT IS POWDER COATING? WHY CHOOSE ACL?Services POWDER COATING LIQUID COATING BLASTING Pipeline Services ACL Pipe Line Services Field Coating Services ADVANCED COATING TRAINING TIDAL MARITIME COATINGS LABORATORY RENTAL CUSTOM EQUIPMENT PROOF PLATES ACL specializes in powder coating custom solutions in Toronto focusing in the following areas; architectural aluminum, corrosion and decorative. Items as small as a pen and as large as a… Read More Automatic Coating Limited has established a reputation as the premier liquid coater in North America & Toronto. ACL has worked on such prestigious project as the Keystone Pipeline, SNC Lavalin… Read More In addition to powder coating applications ACL can also provide blasting services to our customers in Toronto. ACL is equipped with the most diverse blasting equipment under one roof in… Read More PIPE VIPER PipeViper is the only cost effective and portable coating removal system that efficiently addresses all environmental and health and safety concerns in removing virtually any existing coating on… Read More Automatic Coating Limited in Toronto has built countless coating and blasting lines in many facilities. We are experienced in layout flow, equipment design and selection optimizing both new and used,… Read More Automatic Coating Limited (ACL) in Toronto is recognized world wide as having one of the most technologically advanced powder and liquid coating facilities in North America specializing in the application… Read More ACL Toronto also offers our customers the ability to utilize our state of the art testing facilities. The primary focus of the testing laboratory at ACL is to ensure that… Read MoreAutomatic Coating Limited in Toronto has assembled the most up to date collection of rental equipment for you field coating requirements. Automatic Coating can lease compressors, blast equipment and vacuums for… Read More ACL offers a variety of pretreatment and finishing in Toronto. In the pretreatment product category ACL offers a variety of grit blasting and sand blasting machines and chemical washers. With… Read More Automatic Coating provides a variety of inexpensive, high quality proof plates in order for you to meet your colour checking needs in Toronto. ACL proof plates can be utilized for:… Read More PipeViper Brochure View PDF What Customers Say About Us View PDF The PipeViper Coating Removal *patent pending* PipeViper is the only cost effective and portable coating removal system in Toronto… Read More Automatic Coating Limited has invested in state of the art field coating equipment. Automatic Coating Limited has the personnel and project management experience to successfully complete any protective coating project… Read More
Industry Applications Aircraft Architectural CORROSION PROTECTION DEFENSE ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATIONS ELECTRICAL FOOD PROCESSING HEAVY EQUIPMENT Oil, Gas & Water Pipeline Marine CUSTOM ITEMS TRANSPORTATION WIND TURBINE COATING ACL has been awarded the prestigious designation of AS9100 aerospace approved. ACL applies quality powder coating for landing gear parts, moving and structural parts, door handles, struts, hand railings and… Read More ACL provides superior quality in Architectural aluminum meeting AMMA 2603, 2604, 2605 standards, but utilizing an environmentally friendly non chrome system. ACL has provided customers with coatings for balconies, skylights,… Read More ACL has established itself as the gold standard in powder, liquid and pipe coating plants in North America & Toronto. ACL provides quality services to our customers in powder, liquid… Read More ACL is proud of the corrosion control products we have developed and coated for the Naval and Defense industry in Toronto. ACL has provided the patented “tidal coat” system widely… Read More ACL provides solutions and has a complete understanding of the pretreatment, masking & coating requirements for the Electronic & Telecommunications industry, such as PBX telephone equipment in Toronto. Our experience… Read More In the food handling and processing industry ACL has utilized powder and liquid coating to finish food hoppers, vats and other contact parts for the food industry in compliance with… Read More ACL has earned a reputation for being able to complete large and complex assignments. ACL is an innovator in our industry and has the ability to accommodate large heavy equipment,… Read More Automatic Coating has established itself as the premier pipe, pump and miscellaneous fittings for corrosion and chemical resistant coatings in Toronto. ACL had over 40 years’ experience applying F.B.E and… Read More Automatic Coating Limited has established a reputation that is second to none in the marine coatings industry. Automatic Coating Limited has developed and patented coating systems for air intake and uptake louvers… Read More ACL had over 40 years experience applying F.B.E and Liquid coatings to the interior and exterior of pipe & fittings up to 16 feet in diameter and 100 feet in… Read More ACL has been the solutions provider of choice for the transportation industry in Toronto. ACL provides a coating solution that will increase the lifespan on parts while decreasing maintenance costs.… Read More ACL has the most technologically advanced powder and liquid coating facility in Toronto and North America. ACL is certified in Amercoat, International paints, SPC, Carboline, Akzo Nobel & Denso. ACL… Read More ACL has provided coating solutions to the electrical industry. ACL has coated copper and aluminum switch gear/ bus bar for many manufacturers up to 48 kv rating, utilizing fusion bonded… Read More
Quality & SafetyFAQResources Video Gallery GALLERY Projects Newsletter Archive NEWS & EVENTS Automatic Coating Corrosion Protection LinksBlog OpenHomeCareersContactCompany Profile About PIPE LINE COATING Capabilities WHAT IS POWDER COATING? WHY CHOOSE ACL?Services POWDER COATING LIQUID COATING BLASTING Pipeline Services ACL Pipe Line Services Field Coating Services ADVANCED COATING TRAINING TIDAL MARITIME COATINGS LABORATORY RENTAL CUSTOM EQUIPMENT PROOF PLATESIndustry Applications Aircraft Architectural CORROSION PROTECTION DEFENSE ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATIONS Industry Applications Electrical FOOD PROCESSING HEAVY EQUIPMENT Oil, Gas & Water Pipeline Marine CUSTOM ITEMS TRANSPORTATION WIND TURBINE COATINGQuality & SafetyFAQResources Video Gallery GALLERY Projects Newsletter Archive NEWS & EVENTS Automatic Coating Corrosion Protection LinksBlogPowder, Liquid & Pipeline Coating Experts REQUEST INFO REQUEST A QUOTE Privacy Policy StatementAutomatic Coating Limited is committed to safeguarding the personal information of our customers, suppliers and employees.ACL adheres to all provisions of the privacy act and will not share personal information without prior consent. All information collected will only be utilized for the purposes it was originally intended.Any inquiries with regards to the privacy policy can be directed to our privacy officer, Jocelyn Williams,Jocelyn@Automaticcoating.com.
BackACL Shop Services POWDER COATING LIQUID COATING BLASTING Pipeline Services ADVANCED COATING TRAINING TIDAL MARITIME COATINGS LABORATORY RENTAL CUSTOM EQUIPMENT PROOF PLATESRequest More Info
Comments* SubmitPlease wait...
ACL Gallery
View more Gallery
TopHomeServicesPackaging & ShippingCustomer SupportCareersPrivacy StatementCompany ProfileIndustry ApplicationsQuality & SafetyFAQResourcesBlogContactSite mapFollow Us On :
Mail Us : info@automaticcoating.comCall Us : 416-335-7500211 Nugget Avenue Toronto, Ontario M1S 3B1
info@automaticcoating.com 416-335-7500211 Nugget Avenue Toronto, Ontario M1S 3B1© 2020 Corrosion Protection Company, Powder Coating, Liquid Coating - Automatic Coating Limited, Toronto Powered by TechWyse
